booshaka.com 2012-11-15

# Privacy Policy - Booshaka

Booshaka respects your privacy. This Privacy Statement informs you of our privacy practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected online and how that information is used. This statement is readily available on our home page and at the bottom of every Booshaka page.

  * Sites covered by this Privacy Statement
  * Collection of personal information
  * How we use your information
  * How we share your information
  * Children's privacy
  * Your choices and selecting your privacy preferences
  * Access to and accuracy of your information
  * Keeping your information secure
  * Changes to this statement
  * Contacting us

## 1\. Sites covered by this Privacy Statement

This Privacy Statement applies to all Booshaka-owned websites and domains and the websites and domains of our wholly owned subsidiaries ("Booshaka website"), except that a privacy policy or statement posted on Booshaka websites specific to a particular Booshaka program or service will apply instead of this Privacy Statement.

### Links to non-Booshaka websites

The Booshaka website may provide links to third-party websites for your convenience and information. If you access those links, you will leave the Booshaka website. Booshaka does not control those sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from Booshaka's practices. We do not endorse or make any representations about third-party websites. The personal data you choose to provide to or that is collected by these third parties is not covered by the Booshaka Privacy Statement. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any company before submitting your personal information.

We may also provide social media features on our website that enable you to share Booshaka information with your social networks and to interact with Booshaka on various social media sites. Your use of these features may result in the collection or sharing of information about you, depending on the feature. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and settings on the social media sites with which you interact to make sure you understand the information that could be shared by those sites.

## 2\. Collection of personal information

To serve you better and understand your needs and interests, Booshaka collects, exports, and uses personal information with adequate notice and consent, along with required filings with data protection authorities, when applicable. For example, when you order products or services, request information, subscribe to marketing or support materials, register yourself or your Booshaka products, enter contests or participate in surveys, or apply for a job at Booshaka, we will ask you to provide personal information to complete these transactions. The types of personal information you provide to us on these pages may include contact information such as your name, address, telephone number, and email address; financial information such as your credit card number; and other unique information such as user IDs and passwords, billing and transaction information, product and service preferences, contact preferences, educational and employment background, and job interest data.

If you post, comment or share personal information, including photographs, to any public forum on an Booshaka site, social network, blog, or other such forum, please be aware that any personal information you submit can be read, viewed, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to contact you, send you unsolicited messages, or for purposes that neither you nor Booshaka have control over. Booshaka is not responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these forums.

In addition to the information you provide, Booshaka may also collect information during your visit to a Booshaka website, or a website 'powered by' another company on behalf of Booshaka, through our Automatic Data Collection Tools, which include Web beacons, cookies, embedded Web links, and other information-gathering tools. These tools collect certain traffic information that your browser sends to a website, such as your browser type and language, access times, and the address of the website from which you arrived . They may also collect information about your Internet Protocol (IP) address, click stream behavior (i.e. the pages you view, the links you click, and other actions you take in connection with Booshaka websites or 'powered by' websites) and product information. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web, allowing Web servers to locate and identify your computer. Computers use IP addresses to communicate on the Internet, allowing users to browse and shop. Booshaka may also use some of these Automatic Data Collection Tools in connection with certain emails sent from Booshaka and therefore may collect information using these tools when you open the email or click on a link contained in the email.

Booshaka also collects information from commercially available sources that it deems credible. Such information may include your name, address, email address and demographic data. The information Booshaka collects from its commercial sources may be used along with the information Booshaka collects when you visit Booshaka's websites. For example, Booshaka may compare the geographic information acquired from commercial sources with the IP address collected by Automatic Data Collection Tools to derive your general geographic area. 

## 3\. How we use your information

The information Booshaka collects to understand your needs and interests helps Booshaka deliver a consistent and personalized experience. For example, Booshaka may use your information to 

  * assist you in completing a transaction or order;
  * prevent and detect security threats, fraud or other malicious activity;
  * communicate with you about products and services;
  * provide service and support;
  * update you on new services and benefits;
  * provide personalized promotional offers;
  * select content to be communicated to you;
  * personalize some Booshaka websites;
  * measure performance of marketing initiatives, ads, and websites 'powered by' another company on Booshaka's behalf
  * allow you to participate in contests and surveys; and
  * contact you regarding Booshaka products or services.

We will give you the opportunity to choose your privacy preferences regarding the communications we send (see Your choices and selecting your privacy preferences).

The testimonials posted on our Web site are only posted with the expressed permission of the individual or company who provided that testimonial.

Credit card information is used only for payment processing and fraud prevention. Credit card information and other sensitive personal information required to process a credit decision is not used for any other purpose by our financial services providers or Booshaka and will not be kept longer than necessary for providing the services, unless you ask us to retain your credit card information for future purchases.

## 4\. How we share your information

Booshaka will not sell, rent or lease your personal information to others except as described in this Statement. Booshaka shares personal information in the following ways: 

Booshaka retains service providers and suppliers to deliver complete products, services and customer solutions and to assist Booshaka with marketing and communication initiatives. These providers and suppliers include, for example, credit card processors, providers of customer support and live-help, marketing, email service providers, automated data processors, and shipping agents. Suppliers and service providers are required by contract to keep confidential the information received on behalf of Booshaka and may not use it for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for Booshaka.

From time to time, Booshaka participates in marketing initiatives with other companies, including websites 'powered by' another company on behalf of Booshaka. As part of these initiatives, certain Booshaka services and marketing communications may be delivered at the same time as those from other companies. Some of these services and communications offer you the option to share personal information with both Booshaka and the other companies participating in these initiatives. For example, you may receive marketing communications from Booshaka and other companies or have the opportunity to register online for software products from multiple companies. If you choose to provide personal information only to Booshaka, Booshaka will not share this information with the other companies participating in that marketing initiative. If you choose to provide personal information to the other companies, that personal information will be handled according to the privacy policy of those companies which may differ from Booshaka's policies and practices.

Booshaka will require the export of your personal information to other Booshaka-owned business entities in the US and Worldwide in accordance with this Statement to satisfy your request. Such export is a requirement of providing the information to Booshaka.

Except as described in this Statement, Booshaka will not share the personal information you provide to Booshaka with non-Booshaka third parties without your permission, unless to: (i) respond to duly authorized information requests of police and governmental authorities; (ii) comply with any law, regulation, subpoena, or court order; (iii) investigate and help prevent security threats, fraud or other malicious activity; (iv) enforce/protect the rights and properties of Booshaka or its subsidiaries; or (v) protect the rights or personal safety of Booshaka employees and third parties on or using Booshaka property.

Circumstances may arise where, whether for strategic or other business reasons, Booshaka decides to sell, buy, merge or otherwise reorganize businesses in some countries. Such a transaction may involve the disclosure of personal information to prospective or actual purchasers, or the receipt of it from sellers. It is Booshaka's practice to seek appropriate protection for information in these types of transactions.

## 5\. Children's privacy

Booshaka does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and does not target its websites to children under 13. We encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests.

## 6\. Your choices and selecting your privacy preferences

Booshaka gives you the choice of receiving a variety of information that complements our products and services. You can subscribe to receive certain product- and service-specific information and also choose to receive Booshaka general communications. We give you a choice regarding delivery of Booshaka general communications by postal mail, email, telephone, and mobile device.

You can make or change your choices about receiving either subscription or general communications at the data collection point or by using other methods, which are listed in the following sections. This option does not apply to communications primarily for the purpose of administering order completion, contracts, support, product safety warnings, driver updates, or other administrative and transactional notices as the primary purpose of these communications is not promotional in nature.

The communications that you receive from Booshaka will be provided in accordance with this statement. Some communications may utilize automatic data collection tools.

### Subscription communications

Subscription communications include email newsletters, software updates, etc. that may be expressly requested by you or which you consented to receive. After you request such communications, you may opt out of receiving them by using one of the following methods:

  * Select the email 'opt out' or 'unsubscribe' link, or follow the opt-out instructions included in each email subscription communication.
  * To unsubscribe from messages delivered to mobile devices, reply to the message with the words 'STOP' or 'END'.
  * Return to the Web page(s) where you originally registered your preferences and follow the opt-out instructions.
  * Write an email to [Booshaka](mailto:info@booshaka.com). Be sure to provide your name, relevant contact information, and specific relevant information about the Booshaka subscriptions that you no longer wish to receive. 

Please be aware that when you opt out of receiving certain subscription communications, it may affect the services you have chosen to receive from Booshaka where accepting the communications is a condition of receiving the services. 

### Booshaka general communications

Booshaka general communications provide information about products, services, and/or support. This may include new product information, special offers, or invitations to participate in market research.

## 7\. Access to and accuracy of your information

Booshaka strives to keep your personal information accurately recorded. We have implemented technology, management processes and policies to help maintain data accuracy. Booshaka provides individuals with reasonable access to personal information that they provided to Booshaka and the reasonable ability to review and correct it or ask for anonymization, blockage, or deletion, as applicable. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity, such as requiring a password and user ID, before granting access to your data. To view and change the personal information that you directly provided to Booshaka you can return to the Web page where you originally submitted your data and follow the instructions on that Web page or write an email to [Booshaka](mailto:info@booshaka.com).

## 8\. Keeping your personal information secure

Booshaka takes seriously the trust you place in us. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, to maintain data accuracy, and to ensure the appropriate use of the information, Booshaka utilizes appropriate physical, technical and administrative procedures to safeguard the information we collect.

When collecting or transferring sensitive information such as credit card information we use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. The personal information you provide us is stored on computer systems located in controlled facilities which have limited access. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as credit card number or password) over the internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

Credit card numbers are used only for processing payments and are not used for other purposes. As part of real-time payment processing, Booshaka subscribes to a fraud management service. This service gives you and Booshaka an extra level of security to guard against credit card fraud and to protect your financial data. 

## 9\. Changes to this statement

If we change our privacy statement, we will post the revised statement here, with an updated revision date. If we make significant changes to our statement, we may also notify you by other means, such as sending an email or posting a notice on our home page.

## 10\. Contacting us

We value your opinions. If you have comments or questions about our privacy statement, please send them to [Booshaka](mailto:info@booshaka.com).
